这个过程的最后一部分是什么
the last part of the process is what
在我们的观察者眼中继续
goes on in the eyes of the observer we
将此称为响应等
refer to this as the response and like
响应的一切都是
everything else the response is a
波长λ的函数
function of the wavelength lambda in
事实上可以写出这个回应
fact the response can be written this
这是波长的积分
way it is the integral over wavelengths
光的入射光谱
of the spectrum of the incoming light of
反射率和反应
the reflectance and of the response of
那个特别的光明之眼
the eye to light at that particular
波长所以我们所感受到的
wavelength so what we sense in the
我们背后的感光细胞
photoreceptor cells in the back of our
眼睛基本上就是这样的结果
eye is essentially the result of this
特别是积分让我们看看如何
particular integral let's see how that
这里的作品是一张剖面图
works here is a cutaway diagram of the
我们眼睛后方的人眼
human eye at the back of the eye we have
视网膜我们正在看表面
the retina we're looking at the surface
视网膜我们看到很多血
of the retina we see a lot of blood
血管，我们可以看到视神经
vessels and we can see the optic nerve
这是将眼睛与我们联系起来的东西
which is what connects the eye to our
如果我们采取横截面通过大脑
brain if we take a cross-section through
视网膜在那里切片
the retina where to slice through there
我们向下看，我们看到有
we look downwards we see that there are
神经层和其他类型的
layers of nerves and other sorts of
细胞和在这个堆栈的底部我们
cells and at the bottom of this stack we
有光敏细胞和它们
have the light-sensitive cells and they
看起来像这样
look something like this
所以令人惊讶的是
so what's quite surprising is that the
光敏细胞不在
light-sensitive cells are not on the
他们实际上是视网膜的表面
surface of the retina they are actually
在表面下约500微米
about 500 micrometers below the surface
视网膜，所以光线落在上面
of the retina so the light that falls on
视网膜必须向下挣扎
the retina has to fight its way down
通过血管和神经细胞
through blood vessels and nerve cells
以及各种各样的事情
and all sorts of things to get to the
光敏棒和锥形细胞让我们
light-sensitive rod and cone cells let's
看看他们就是这些杆细胞
look at the rod cells they're these
我们看到的小虫形物体
small worm shaped objects that we see in
他们包含视网膜的背面
the back of the retina they contain a
化学物质叫做视紫红质，相当
chemical called rhodopsin and is quite
一个重要的化学品，因为当a
an important chemical because when a
光子照射它会改变它
photon of light hits it it changes its
形状从它改变形状
shape it changes its shape from this to
我们可以看到它的一只手臂
that and we can see the one arm of the
事实上，分子是被旋转的
molecule is in fact being spun around by
光子的影响就是这样
the impact of the photon and that is
最终转变为电气
eventually converted into an electrical
沿光学传播的信号
signal which travels along the optical
神经到你大脑的视觉皮层
nerve to the visual cortex of your brain
杆细胞非常敏感
the rod cells are very very sensitive to
因此这些是我们使用的细胞
light so these are the cells we use in
我们使用的低光条件
low-light conditions what we use at
晚上和他们有线的方式
night and the way they're wired makes
他们也非常敏感
them also very sensitive to
这是我们用来确定的
that's what we use to determine
一些东西在我们的边缘移动
something's moving in the edge of our
视杆细胞是
field of view the rod cells are
对一系列电磁敏感
sensitive to a range of electromagnetic
辐射如此图所示
radiation as shown by this graph here so
这是杆的响应曲线
this is the response curve of the rod
细胞我们用符号M表示它
cells and we denote it by the symbol M
它当然是一个功能
and it of course is a function of
波长λ为棒状细胞
wavelength lambda the rod cells are
最大响应498的光
maximally responsive to light at 498
纳米基本上是中灰色
nanometers basically mid gray in color
另一类非常重要的细胞
the other very important class of cells
在人眼中是锥细胞和
in the human eye are the cone cells and
其中一个在这里表明他们不是
one of them's indicated here they're not
圆锥形的，只有更加丰富的
that conical there's only fatter at the
比他们在顶部相当低
bottom than they are at the top quite a
不同形状的棒状细胞
different shape to the rod cells the
锥细胞含有被称为敌人的化学物质
cone cells contain chemicals called foe
与视紫红质有关的毒素
toxins that are related to rhodopsin
我们在杆细胞中有
that we have in the rod cells there are
不同口味的毒素
different flavors of the toxins that are
敏感的光线不同的颜色
sensitive to light different colors the
锥形细胞是我们用于我们的
cone cells are what we use for our
日常的白天活动
everyday daytime activities in the
白天我们使用的是锥形细胞而不是
daytime we use our cone cells not the
棒细胞锥细胞含有
rod cells the cone cells contain a
被称为毒素毒素的化学物质是
chemical called fo toxin foe toxin is
与视紫红质有关但有三种
related to rhodopsin but there are three
不同种类的法塔赫人
different flavors of fatah persons the
对红色敏感的毒素
toxins that are sensitive to red to
绿色和蓝色的光，所以有
green and to blue light so there are
三种不同类型的锥体
three different types of cones those
包含这些不同的东西
that are that contain these different
对红色敏感的法塔赫人的类型
types of fatah person sensitive to red
绿色和蓝色，所以我们说人类
green and blue so we say that human
众生是三色，这意味着我们拥有
beings are trichromats it means we have
得到了可以感知三种不同的细胞
got cells that can sense three different
颜色
colors
敏感的内部不同的乐队
sensitive to different bands within the
频谱，这就是所显示的
spectrum and that's what's shown in the
这里的图通常是这些乐队
graph over here often these bands are
由字母sm和L引用
referred to by the letters s m and L
它代表短波长介质
which stands for short wavelength medium
波长和长波长
wavelength and long wavelength
我们也将它们称为蓝绿色和
we'd also refer them as blue green and
红色按此顺序响应
red in that order the response of the
短的中长锥细胞
short medium and long cone cells as
这里显示我们可以看到相当的
shown here we can see that there's quite
有些重叠尤其是
some overlap particularly between the
中长波锥细胞
medium and long wavelength cones cells
并且在此处显示以供参考
and also shown here for reference is the
我们看到的杆细胞的反应
response of the rod cells we looked at
在上一张幻灯片中，让我们看看更多
in the previous slide let's look more
紧靠视网膜
closely at the retina
并且有两个关键的地标
and there are two key landmarks in the
视网膜一是我们所说的中央凹
retina one is what we call the fovea
我们集中精力的地方
where we have an enormous concentration
光敏细胞和另一个
of light-sensitive cells and the other
光学所在的大地标
big landmark which is where the optic
神经加入视网膜，该区域有
nerve joins the retina and that area has
几乎没有光敏细胞
almost no light sensitive cells exactly
你眼中的一个盲点，如果我们
a blind spot in your eye so if we
预测这两点我们
project those two points down and we
绘制一个我们可以绘制的轴
draw an axis we can plot the
锥细胞密度的浓度
concentration for density of cone cells
作为角度的函数远离
as a function of angle away from the
我们有一方的中央凹等等
fovea and so on one side we have the
另一方面，你的耳朵方向
direction towards your ear on the other
我们有朝向你的方向
side we have the direction towards your
鼻子，我们可以看到有一个巨大的
nose and we can see there's an enormous
中央凹区锥体的浓度
concentration of cones in the fovea area
并且浓度低得多
and a much lower concentration of cone
在你的眼睛的细胞我们是什么
cells in the rest of your eye what we
如果我们打电话给周边视野区域
call the peripheral vision area if we
现在看看杆细胞的分布
look now the distribution of rod cells
我们看到几乎与我们看到的相反
we see almost the converse we see that
在这里有很多杆细胞
there are very many rod cells in the
视力的周边部分不是太多
peripheral part of vision not too many
在你的恐惧症中它们都是如此
of them at all in your phobia so the
我们的浓度非常高
fovea we have a very high concentration
其余的颜色敏感细胞
of color sensitive cells the rest of the
眼睛里有大量的细胞
eye there are a large number of cells
对光敏感的
that are sensitive to light
but don't distinguish between different
但不要区分不同
颜色
colors